

# ANNA MAULIDITA WIDY ANGGRAENA

Karet Tengsin, Tanah Abang, Central Jakarta, 10220, Indonesia

linkedin.com/in/anna-maulidita-widy-anggraena-1659b51b5/ | +6281243714829 | mauliditaanna@gmail.com

#### **PROFILE**

I'm Anna, currently studying for a bachelor's degree at the State University of Jakarta (UNJ), Informatics and Computer Engineering Education Department. I am quite skilled, hardworker, able to work under pressure and work well together. I want to develop my knowledge and skills in IT field at Technology Startup environment. Experienced in working directly with clients to ensure all the goals of a project are achieved and met within scope and budget.

#### **EDUCATION**

## Universitas Negeri Jakarta

Bachelor's Degree Informatics and Computer Engineering

Sep 2020 - Present

# SMA Negeri 7 Bogor

Natural Science Major

Jul 2017 - Dec 2020

#### **INTERNSHIPS**

# \* Software Developer at PT. Cakra Wijaya Solusi

- Analyzed government procurement of goods and services websites
- Created a Galenium Pharmasia Website
- Created a CRUD Customer Website
- Learned and implement corporate swagger and keycloak templates
- Designed an interactive virtual room using Sketchup App & HomebyMe Website
- Created a Jaya Makmur Furnindo Website
- Designed an Company Profile brochure

# **EMPLOYMENT HISTORY**

# Waitress, Mie Gacoan Padjajaran Bogor

Increased the percentage of customers who provided positive reviews

- Successfully boosted sales through additional orders and menu recommendations.
- Established good teamwork and collaboration with the kitchen staff and fellow servers to ensure smooth operations and deliver high-quality service.
- Successfully completed internal training programs to enhance service skills and product knowledge.

# Freelanced at PUBG Mobile Indonesia National Championship (PINC)

Tennis Indoor Stadium, Jakarta

- · Achieved the set ticket sales targets established by the tournament organizers.
- Successfully sold a significant number of tickets, making a significant contribution to the success of the event.
- Maintained good customer relationships by providing friendly service and assisting with ticket-related inquiries.

East Jakarta

GPA: 8.6/10.0

Feb 2023 - Aug 2023

Central Jakarta

Aug 2022 - Nov 2022

Apr 2019

Bogor

#### **EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES**

ERA-FM (Educational Radio) UNJ

Created a playlists of songs according to radio brodcasts & hotlock

Oct 2020 - Jan 2022 Music Director

Paduan Suara SMAN 7 Bogor

Dec 2017 - Dec 2020 Soprano

# **COURSES**

Pemrograman Bahasa Java & C at Dicoding

Sep 2021 - Dec 2021

Fundamental Front-End Development at Dicoding

June 2022 - Sep 2022

Laravel, ReactJS, ReactNative Fundamentals Programming at Camp404

Nov 2022 - Feb 2023

# **LANGUAGES**

Indonesia ..... English .....

#### **SKILLS**

Microsoft Office ..... HTML & CSS ..... Javascript ..... Basic Java Language ..... Basic C Language ...... Framework ReactJS .....

Node IS

Basic VueJS .....

# **COMMITEE ACTIVITIES**

## Dekan Cup Fakultas Teknik UNJ 2022

Oct 2022 - Nov 2022 Mobile Legend's Subdivision Head

- Promoted on personal Social Media (Instagram), so that is exceeds the target by 120%
- Created booklet, match rundowns, bracket, and budget estimates

## Informatics Super League PTIK & STI 2021

• Created a booklet, match rundowns, bracket, and budget estimates.

# Orientasi Radio Komunitas ERA-FM UNJ 2021

• Created and distributed meeting invitation & follow up participants.

# Public Relations

# Pelatihan Kepemimpinan Mahasiswa prodi Rumpun Teknik Elektro (PKMP RTE) 2021

- Created a rules, guidebooks, and assigned grades
- Supervised Participants
- Imposed sanctions

## Pengenalan Kehidupan Kampus Mahasiswa Baru (PKKMB PTIK 2021)

Aug 2021

Nov 2021

- Created a rules, guidebooks, and assigned grades
- Supervised Participants
- Imposed sanctions

# Musyawarah Besar ERAFM UNJ 2021

- Succeeded in preventing a fund deficit, create a real estimate of cost treasurer accountability report (RAB)
- Created licensing letters, activity proposals, request for funds, attendance of participants and committees, invitations to briefing & evaluation meetings, record and share meeting result.

Dec 2020 - June 2021 Treasurer & Deputy Secretary

Nov 2021 - Dec 2021

Mobile Legend's Subdivision Head

Dicipline and Assessment Team

Dicipline and Assessment Team

Oct 2021 - Nov 2021